iambic.com 2011-05-25

# iambic, Inc. - Privacy Policy

|    
  
|  |    
|   
---  
| 

|  |  |  **Privacy Policy**  
---|---  
  
* * *  
  
iambic, Inc. takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. **What this Privacy Policy covers**
* This Privacy Policy covers iambic treatment of personally identifiable information that iambic collects when you are on the iambic site, and when you use iambic services.
* This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that iambic does not own or control, or to people that iambic does not employ or manage.

**Information Collection and Use**

* iambic, Inc. collects personally identifiable information when you register for an iambic account, when you use certain iambic products or services and when you visit iambic pages. iambic, Inc. may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners. 
* When you register with iambic, we ask for a certain amount of personal information. Once you register with iambic and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 
* iambic, Inc. also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address. 
* iambic, Inc. uses information for three general purposes: to constantly improve its services and products, to fulfill your requests regarding its products and to contact you about special offers and new products. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

  * **Under no circumstances iambic will sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone.**
  * **All registration information you provide is confidential and is used for internal purposes only.**

**Cookies**

  * iambic may set and access iambic cookies on your computer. 

**Your Ability to Edit Your Account Information and Preferences**

  * iambic, Inc. gives you the ability to edit your iambic Account Information and preferences at any time, including whether you want iambic to contact you about specials and new products. 

**Security**

  * Your iambic account Information is password-protected for your privacy and security. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

  * iambic, Inc. may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes you will be promptly notified. 

If you have further questions or doubts regarding this policy feel free to contact our customer service department.
